Guide to the Jacki Apple Papers MSS.173
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IX. Business Correspondence
  - University of Wisconsin, Madison and Milwaukee, 1981-1987; cuid21046 (Box 7)
  - Utica College/Ithaca College (New York), 1976-1980; cuid21047 (Box 7)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University, 1980-1990; cuid21048 (Box 7)
  - Women Artists Archive (SUNY, Oswego; New York), 1990; cuid21049 (Box 7)
  - Neil Bartlett (London), 1982; cuid21050 (Box 7)
  - H. Besacier (Lyon, France), 1978; cuid21051 (Box 7)
  - Nancy Buchanan (New York, Los Angeles), 1980; cuid21052 (Box 7)
  - California Tour: J. Simonian, SSB Susan Martin, 1979; cuid21053 (Box 7)
  - Alvin Curran, 1977; cuid21054 (Box 7)
  - Peter Hamilton (Melbourne, Australia), 1980; cuid21055 (Box 7)
  - Ian Hunter (National Gallery; Wellington, New Zealand), 1979-1982; cuid21056 (Box 7)
  - Jeff Gordon, 1982-1983; cuid21057 (Box 7)
  - Michael Kaspar, 1981; cuid21058 (Box 7)
  - Jane Kent and Anne Marsh (Perth, Australia), 1982; cuid21059 (Box 7)
  - Henry Korn (New York City), 1981-1982; cuid21060 (Box 7)
  - Italian Curators and Writers, 1976-1980; cuid21061 (Box 7)
  - John Lethbridge (Sydney, Australia), 1978; cuid21062 (Box 7)
  - Peter Meyer (Stockholm, Sweden), 1983-1985; cuid21063 (Box 7)
  - Jill Scott (Australia), 1978; cuid21064 (Box 7)
  - Patricia Tavener (Oakland, California), 1978; cuid21065 (Box 7)
  - Geraldine Waxkovsky (Boulder, Colorado), 1979; cuid21066 (Box 7)
  - Faith Wilding and Everett Frost (Los Angeles), 1980-1981; cuid21067 (Box 7)
  - Eva Yuen (Hong Kong), 1981; cuid21068 (Box 7)
  - A.I.R. (New York City), 1982; cuid21069 (Box 7)
  - Executive Arts Consultation Proposal, 1978-1979; cuid21070 (Box 7)
  - Harvestworks, Tellus (New York City), 1985-1995; cuid21071 (Box 7)
  - Franklin Furnace (New York City), 1982; cuid21072 (Box 7)
  - Irvine Fine Arts Center (California): "Maps, Charts, and Routes" Exhibition, 1996; cuid21073 (Box 7)
  - Mercer Union (Toronot): "Love Gasoline" Exhibition, 1996; cuid21074 (Box 7)
  - N23 Correspondence, 1981; cuid21075 (Box 7)
  - N23 Proposals, 1981; cuid21076 (Box 7)
  - NASA, 1981; cuid21077 (Box 7)
  - Nexus Contemporary Arts Center (Atlanta), 1986; cuid21078 (Box 7)
  - One Ten Records (New York City), 1977-1980; cuid21079 (Box 7)
  - San Francisco Cameraworks, 1985; cuid21080 (Box 8)
  - Western Front (Vancouver), 1988-1989; cuid21081 (Box 8)
  - Fireworks (Los Angeles), 1999; cuid21082 (Box 8)
  - Fresno Arts Center and Museum (California), 1986-1987; cuid21083 (Box 8)
  - Half a Dozen Rose Gallery (Los Angeles), 1996; cuid21084 (Box 8)
  - Mary Delahoyd Gallery (New York City), 1985; cuid21085 (Box 8)
  - MOCA (Los Angeles), 1998-2005; cuid21086 (Box 8)
  - Museum of Contemporary Hispanic Art (New York City), 1986; cuid21087 (Box 8)
  - Newport Harbor Museum, 1988-1990; cuid21088 (Box 8)
  - Santa Monica Museum of Art Proposal, 1988; cuid21089 (Box 8)
  - Rhode Island School of Design (RISD), 1991; cuid21090 (Box 8)
  - San Jose State University (California), 1982; cuid21091 (Box 8)
  - Rutgers University (Mark Berger), 1980; cuid21092 (Box 8)
  - Scripts College and Claremont Colleges, 1994; cuid21093 (Box 8)
  - Simon Fraser University (Vancouver), 1979; cuid21094 (Box 8)
  - After Image (Publication, 1983-1985; cuid21095 (Box 8)
  - University of Kansas, 1997; cuid21096 (Box 8)
  - Mindy Affirme, 1980; cuid21097 (Box 8)
  - Dena Hawes, 1995-1997; cuid21098 (Box 8)
  - Lynn Hershman, 1978; cuid21099 (Box 8)
  - Beryl Spector (PBS), 1980; cuid21100 (Box 8)
  - Blue Gene Tyranny (Mills College; Oakland, California), 1978; cuid21101 (Box 8)
  - Brody Arts Fund (Los Angeles), 1986-1988; cuid21102 (Box 8)
  - California Community Foundation, 1996-2001; cuid21103 (Box 8)
  - Durfee Foundation, 2003-2007; cuid21104 (Box 8)
  - Flintridge Foundation (Pasadena, California), 2000-2005; cuid21105 (Box 8)
  - J. Paul Getty Trust Fund for the Arts, 1989; cuid21106 (Box 8)
  - Guggenheim Foundation Fellowships, 1982-2000; cuid21107 (Box 8)
  - LACE Project Grants, 1986-1990; cuid21108 (Box 8)
  - MacArthur Foundation, 1992-2000; cuid21109 (Box 8)
  - McKnight Foundation (Minneapolis, Minnesota), 1999; cuid21110 (Box 8)
  - The Artists Foundation (Massachusetts Arts Council), 1988; cuid21111 (Box 8)
  - California Arts Council, 1987; cuid21112 (Box 8)
  - CAPS (Creative Artists Program Services)/NYSCA, 1978-1983; cuid21113 (Box 9)
  - CPB (Corporation for Public Broadcasting)/NPR Radio Production Grant, 1986; cuid21114 (Box 9)
  - Cultural Affairs Department, City of Los Angeles -- Individual Artists, 1996-2000; cuid21115 (Box 9)
  - Cultural Affairs Department, City of Los Angeles -- Public Arts Division, 2000-2006; cuid21116 (Box 9)
  - Cultural Affairs Department, City of Los Angeles -- Regional Arts, 2000; cuid21117 (Box 9)
  - Illinois Arts Council, 1996; cuid21118 (Box 9)
  - Los Angeles County Music and Performing Arts Commission, 1988; cuid21119 (Box 9)
  - Los Angeles Endowment for the Arts, 1989-1990; cuid21120 (Box 9)
  - Massachusetts Arts Council Radio Panel, 1989; cuid21121 (Box 9)
  - METRO Arts, Los Angeles, 2000-2003; cuid21122 (Box 9)
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) - Services to the Field, 1980-1981; cuid21123 (Box 9)
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) - Visual Arts Fellowship, 1979-1981; cuid21124 (Box 9)
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) - Visual Arts New Genres, 1978-1995; cuid21125 (Box 9)
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) - Inter-Arts Collaborations, 1984; cuid21126 (Box 9)
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) - Inter-Arts (Cactus), 1989-1993; cuid21127 (Box 9)
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) - Media Arts/Radio, 1985-1993; cuid21128 (Box 10)
  - National/State/County Partnership Grants (Cactus Foundation), 1987-1989; cuid21129 (Box 10)
  - Santa Monica Arts Commission - Cactus Performances, 1988-1989; cuid21130 (Box 10)
  - Santa Monica Arts Commission - Public Art Proposal, 1988-2004; cuid21131 (Box 10)
  - Seattle Arts Commission (Panelist), 1991; cuid21132 (Box 10)
  - Western States Arts Federation (Regional NEA), 1996; cuid21133 (Box 10)
  - Martin Luther King Community Center Public Art Project, 2002-2003; cuid21134 (Box 10)
  - Queen Anne Community Center Public Art Project, 2001-2004; cuid21135 (Box 10)
  - Oakwood-Venice Public Art -- Concepts and Visual Docs, 1999-2003; cuid21136 (Box 10)
  - Oakwood-Venice Public Art -- Research, Oral History, Interviews, and Notes, 1999-2003; cuid21137 (Box 10)
  - Oakwood-Venice Public Art -- Contracts, Receipts, Legal, Ledtters, 1999-2003; cuid21138 (Box 10)
  - Aliso Pico Public Art Project -- Concept, Design, Production with Eric Mar, 1998-1999; cuid21139 (Box 10)
  - Aliso Pico Public Art Project -- Announcement, Public Relations, 1998-1999; cuid21140 (Box 10)
  - Aliso Pico Public Art Project -- Contracts, Legal, 1998-1999; cuid21141 (Box 10)
  - Little Tokyo Public Library (Los Angeles) -- City Correspondence, Design Concepts, 2001-2005; cuid21142 (Box 11)
  - Little Tokyo Public Library (Los Angeles) -- Research and Receipts, 2001-2005; cuid21143 (Box 11)
  - Little Tokyo Public Library (Los Angeles) -- Contracts, 2002-2005; cuid21144 (Box 11)
  - Center for Cultural Innovation, Investing in Artists Grants, 2007-2008; cuid21145 (Box 11)
  - Patrick Tofts (English) -- Art Director Friend (Persona), 1978-1989; cuid21146 (Box 11)
  - Alice Hutchinson (Art Historian, Curator, Friend), 1990s; cuid21147 (Box 11)
  - Heike Strelow (Frankfurt, Germany), 1997; cuid21148 (Box 11)
  - Bruce Odland, 1990s; cuid21149 (Box 11)
  - Lou Mallozzi -- Recommendations, 1992-1993; cuid21150 (Box 11)
  - Kathie Rae Huffman -- Projects, Russia, High Performance, World Art, 1994-1996; cuid21151 (Box 11)
  - The New Museum of Contemporary Art (New York City), 1984-1986; cuid21152 (Box 11)
  - AART (Audio Art Transmissions); Irish Museum of Modern Art (Dublin), 1990-1994; cuid21153 (Box 11)
  - Sveska Gallery (Prague), 1997-1998; cuid21154 (Box 11)
  - Next Monet (Online Gallery), 1999; cuid21155 (Box 11)
  - CDs -- Audio Works -- Press Releases, 1991; cuid21156 (Box 11)
  - Exhibition, Etc. Announcement, 1990s; cuid21157 (Box 11)
  - Christ of Migone (Radio Montreal), 1992; cuid21158 (Box 11)
  - Cleveland Center for Contemporary Art (Exhibition/Performance Advisory Committee), 1992-1993; cuid21159 (Box 11)
  - Cleveland Performance Art Festival, 1989-1995; cuid21160 (Box 11)
  - Sound Culture -- The Performance Space (Australia), 1990-1991; cuid21161 (Box 12)
  - Artspace (Auckland, New Zealand) -- Performance Correspondence, Soundwatch, 1993-1994; cuid21162 (Box 12)
  - Arroyo Arts -- River Vision Project, 2000; cuid21163 (Box 12)
  - Arroyo Arts -- "Without Alarm" Exhibition Sanctuary Piece, 1996; cuid21164 (Box 12)
  - Huntington Beach Art Center -- "Are We Touched?" Group Show, 1997; cuid21165 (Box 12)
  - ATHE (Association for Theater in Higher Ed) -- Laurie Beth Clark Conference, 1995; cuid21166 (Box 12)
  - College Art Association Conference -- Panel on Place of Performance Art in Higher Ed, 1995; cuid21167 (Box 12)
  - School of Art Institute of Chicago -- Experiemental Sound Studio, 1993; cuid21168 (Box 12)
  - Skidmore College, 1998; cuid21169 (Box 12)
  - Cal State University, Los Angeles, 1997; cuid21170 (Box 12)
  - Cal State, Long Beach -- Dance Department Teaching, 1983; cuid21171 (Box 12)
  - Cal State, Long Beach -- Inter-Arts Panel and Advisory Council, 1988-1989; cuid21172 (Box 12)
  - Cal State, Monterey Bay -- Radio Workshop, 2003; cuid21173 (Box 12)
  - Art Center -- Performance Class Posters, Syllabi, Programs, 1991-2012; cuid21174 (Box 12)
  - EARJAM IV -- Tech Scripts and Staging, 2004; cuid21175 (Box 12)
  - EARJAM IV -- Production Notes/Artists Lists, 2004; cuid21176 (Box 12)
  - EARJAM III -- Press Releases, 2002; cuid21177 (Box 12)
  - EARJAM II -- Grant Proposal, Production Notes, 2001; cuid21178 (Box 12)
  - EARJAM I -- Artists Lists, Production Notes, 2000; cuid21179 (Box 12)
  - EARJAM I-IV -- Programs, Press, 2000-2004; cuid21180 (Box 12)
  - ArtCenter -- Collaborative Course Proposal, 2002-2003; cuid21181 (Box 12)
  - ArtCenter -- Film Classes, Chinese Cinema, Women Directors, 1995-2001; cuid21182 (Box 13)
  - ArtCenter -- Dramatic Structures Class, 2002; cuid21183 (Box 13)
  - ArtCenter -- 1960s Cultural History Class -- Postes, 2005; cuid21184 (Box 13)
  - ArtCenter -- Modernism Syllabi, 1990-2014; cuid21185 (Box 13)
  - ArtCenter -- Various Courses, 1983-1993; cuid21186 (Box 13)
  - Flyers, 1990s-2000s; cuid20963 (Box 13)
- Series X. Critical Writing on the Arts
  - Art of Spectacle Catalog (UCLA/LACE), 1984-1985; cuid21187 (Box 13)
  - Art and Auction Magazine, 1984; cuid21188 (Box 13)
  - Art Center College of Design Magazine (Feature Essay), undated; cuid21189 (Box 13)
  - Art Scene, 1984; cuid21190 (Box 13)
  - Artweek, 1982-1990; cuid21191 (Box 13)
  - Artweek (Published), 1983-1990; cuid21192 (Box 13)
  - Astro Arts/Fringe Festvial, 1990; cuid21193 (Box 14)
  - BAM (Brooklyn Academy of Music), 1984; cuid21194 (Box 14)
  - Cal Arts Magazine, 1984; cuid21195 (Box 14)
  - Guggenheim Gallery, Chapman University Exhibition Catalog Essay, 1994; cuid21196 (Box 14)
  - EAR Magazine, 1984; cuid21197 (Box 14)
  - Forecast: Public Art Review, 1994-1995; cuid21198 (Box 14)
  - High Performance -- Features, 1984-1994; cuid21199 (Box 14)
  - High Performance -- Reviews, 1987-1989; cuid21200 (Box 14)
  - High Performance -- Sound Columns, 1990-1994; cuid21201 (Box 14)
  - High Performance -- Writers Correspondence and Rejects, 1994; cuid21202 (Box 14)
  - High Performance -- Media Arts Editor, 1994-1995; cuid21203 (Box 14)
  - High Performance -- Submission, RDA and Meditation, 1990; cuid21204 (Box 14)
  - Images and Issues Magazine, 1982; cuid21205 (Box 14)
  - L.A. Weekly -- General, 1980s; cuid21206 (Box 14)
  - L.A. Weekly -- Short Pieces, 1980s; cuid21207 (Box 15)
  - LAICA Journal, 1979; cuid21208 (Box 15)
  - Media Arts, 1983-1989; cuid21209 (Box 15)
  - New Womens Times, 1979; cuid21210 (Box 15)
  - P-Form Magazine, 1996-1998; cuid21211 (Box 15)
  - Performance Research Journal, 1995; cuid21212 (Box 15)
  - Performing Arts Journal (PAJ), 1995; cuid21213 (Box 15)
  - Preview NYC, 1976; cuid21214 (Box 15)
  - Theater L.A., 1983; cuid21215 (Box 15)
  - TDR - The Drama Review, 1991; cuid21216 (Box 15)
  - Track 16 Press -- Tatti Wattles Book Essay, 1996; cuid21217 (Box 15)
  - Visions Magazine (Los Angeles), 1992-1995; cuid21218 (Box 15)
  - World Art, 1995; cuid21219 (Box 15)
  - Martin Luther King Community Center Public Art Project, 2002-2003; cuid21220 (Box 15)
  - Queen Anne Community Center Public Art Project, 2001-2004; cuid21221 (Box 15)
  - Fabrik, 2010-2016; cuid21222 (Box 16)
  - THE, 2008-2009; cuid21223 (Box 20)
- Series XI. Media Works
  - Redefining Democracy in America (RDA) -- Part 6, A Leap of Faith Original Scripts and Score, 1992; cuid21224 (Box 16)
  - Redefining Democracy in America (RDA) -- Part 6, A Leap of Faith -- General, 1992; cuid21225 (Box 16)
  - Redefining Democracy in America (RDA) -- Part 6, A Leap of Faith -- Video and Work Notes, 1992; cuid21226 (Box 16)
  - Redefining Democracy in America (RDA) -- Part 4, Voices of America, 1992; cuid21227 (Box 16)
  - Redefining Democracy in America (RDA) -- Part 1, 2, 3, Episodes in Black and White -- Original Scripts and Recordings Score, 1991; cuid21228 (Box 16)
  - Redefining Democracy in America (RDA) -- Part 1, 2, 3, Episodes in Black and White -- Original Workbook, 1991; cuid21229 (Box 16)
  - Redefining Democracy in America (RDA) -- Part 1, 2, 3, Episodes in Black and White -- Layouts, 1991; cuid21230 (Box 20)
  - Redefining Democracy in America (RDA) -- CD from TELLUS, 1991; cuid21231 (Box 16)
  - Redefining Democracy in America (RDA) -- Contracts, 1990-1991; cuid21232 (Box 16)
  - Redefining Democracy in America (RDA) -- Part 1, 2, 3, Episodes in Black and White -- General, 1991; cuid21233 (Box 16)
  - Redefining Democracy in America (RDA) -- Parts 7, 8 -- LA Cultural Affairs Grant, 1992; cuid21234 (Box 16)
  - Redefining Democracy in America (RDA) -- Parts 7, 8 -- LACE Artists Project Grant, 1991-1993; cuid21235 (Box 16)
  - Redefining Democracy in America (RDA) -- NEA Grant, 1991-1992; cuid21236 (Box 17)
  - Frenzy in the Night -- Scripts, 1990; cuid21237 (Box 17)
  - Frenzy in the Night -- Contracts, 1990; cuid21238 (Box 17)
  - Redefining Democracy in America Recordings -- Parts 1, 2, 3: Episodes in Black and White -- Broadcast Call-ins (KPFK-FM, Los Angeles), 1991; cuid21239 (Box 18)
  - Redefining Democracy in America Recordings -- Parts 1, 2, 3: Episodes in Black and White -- Part 1, 1991; cuid21240 (Box 18)
  - Redefining Democracy in America Recordings -- Parts 1, 2, 3: Episodes in Black and White -- Part 1 Final Program, 1991; cuid21241 (Box 18)
  - Redefining Democracy in America Recordings -- Parts 1, 2, 3: Episodes in Black and White -- Part 3 Final Program, 1991; cuid21242 (Box 18)
  - Redefining Democracy in America Recordings -- Parts 1, 2, 3: Episodes in Black and White -- Part 1 Compilation for CD Anthology, 1991; cuid21243 (Box 18)
  - Redefining Democracy in America Recordings -- Parts 4, 5: Voices of America -- Live Call-in Broadcasts with Different Hosts (KPFK-FM), 1992; cuid21244 (Box 18)
  - Redefining Democracy in America Recordings -- Parts 4, 5: Voices of America -- Final Program, 1992; cuid21245 (Box 18)
  - Redefining Democracy in America Recordings -- Parts 4, 5: Voices of America -- Production DAT Tapes, 1992; cuid21246 (Box 19)
  - Redefining Democracy in America Recordings -- Part 6: A Leap of Faith -- Dialog, 1992; cuid21247 (Box 19)
  - Redefining Democracy in America Recordings -- Part 6: A Leap of Faith -- Dialog, 1992; cuid21248 (Box 19)
  - Redefining Democracy in America Recordings -- Part 6: A Leap of Faith -- Final, 1992; cuid21249 (Box 19)
  - Redefining Democracy in America Recordings -- Part 6: A Leap of Faith -- Production DAT Tapes of Unrehearsed Conversation between Jacki Apple and Keith Antar Mason, 1992; cuid21250 (Box 19)